You
Whoa, that's weird. I'm shaking
But I felt fine ever since becoming a zombie
Is there something wrong with me?
I have to tell Mr. Kotaro
So looks like we're lost at sea
Well, this is surprising
But which way are we going? Can we get back?
Take it easy. Zombies can't drown, probably
Then let's find an island! We can start all over
Zombie survival, huh? Sounds like fun. Count me in
For starters, we might want to do our makeup in case anything happens
This is a disaster
Damn it, my phone's not working
It's just like the depopulation
The curse that comes with the Reiwa era
A year ago, if we'd fixed it while we were still in Heisei instead
This tragedy could have been stopped
We need to get out of here immediately
Oh, we just ended up back in Saga
And not far from where we started
Come on, I know it's a small place but still
What's in there, Lady Junko?
Oh, those are my tools for making Ozaki dolls.
I was afraid they would get wet.
You're ever the diligent worker, I see.
Hey, what's wrong?
It's about to bite the duck!
Uh-oh. We better go get our crap out. Quick!
Looks like our house is gone, and everything we own.
Our costumes, and Mr. Kotaro's instruments as well.
Wait, oh no! Our makeup too!
That's bad!
I'm so sorry, guys. I should have grabbed that, not my tools.
Well then, things have taken a clear turn for the worse.
If we keep turning toward the worst, maybe we'll do a donut?
I sure hope so.
More importantly, what are we going to do now?
Sanko?
Machiko!
What are you girls doing out here on the beach?
Hishi!
Oh, she works with me at the factory.
I guess our house got washed away.
That big pile of debris was your house?
My goodness, you poor children.
Do you have no place to go?
You should come down to Kation.
It's been turned into a shelter.
Oh, man.
The damage must be much worse than we imagined.
The actual shelter was too much of a mess to stay in, so we're here.
It'll have to do for now.
In times like this, people always tell you,
try to put on a brave face.
But it's hard, you know?
I wonder if Mr. Kotaro is okay.
Sorry.
This is the only space we have for you girls.
Don't be sorry.
We're just relieved.
We're happy you let us borrow the tarp as well.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah, you're the best.
Thank you!
I figure it'll be helpful since you're so popular.
There's cardboard to sit on and blankets downstairs.
Come grab some later.
Oh!
And would you mind introducing everyone, Sanko?
Uh, my name is...
That's Ichiko.
I'm Niko.
And that's Yonko, Itsuko, and Matsuko.
Oh, numerical names.
I'm Machiko.
Wait, where's that...
Zero-ko?
I don't see her.
Here you go, man.
You probably shouldn't eat that, Zero-ko!
We're sorry about her.
Nothing to worry about.
I know you girls have been through a lot.
You must be hungry.
Go ahead.
My, you're even hungrier than I thought, aren't you?
Hi!
Can we help you guys with anything?
Yes, we could definitely use a few extra hands.
Everyone at the factory knows you're a hard worker, Sanko.
And I guess that goes for your friends, too.
But don't wear yourselves out.
The rest of us will be in real trouble without your help.
Oh, you don't have to worry about us.
We're actually dead.
Dead!
Set on working!
Huh?
Oh, rest, rest.
I want to go home now!
Huh?
Please, can we leave?
I'm scared.
Yeah.
Please, can we go home?
One, two, three, four!
Oh, rest, rest.
Okuba!
Hm?
I have an idea of what's happening!
How about is it?
Well, it's all of Saga.
And some neighboring prefectures too.
A bunch of towers are knocked over, so it's not just power, it's internet and phones.
That's just great.
This is why I said we needed a satellite phone for work.
And the roads are a total mess as well.
Apparently in the areas that were hit the hardest, they've got people staying in shelters now.
So, should we split up again?
At Kation in Kuratsu, many citizens are taking shelter.
I'm with NBK Fukuoka.
How would you describe things here, sir?
I gotta tell ya, it's been absolutely wild!
Just look around!
You're looking at the biggest shelter in the area, so all of Saga is here!
I mean, not all of Saga.
But it does feel kinda weird sleeping where you used to shop!
For one thing, I'm going to miss my house.
But still, everybody here is trying their best to stay positive.
If it weren't for that, I probably would've broken down crying by now.
In fact, I know I would've, so I'm grateful to be here.
Well, we're more concerned about kids and the elderly, and we might be here for a while.
We actually have a few kids of our own.
The youngest is two years old, and you wouldn't believe how much that kiddo takes after her mother.
It's really a sight to see.
Luckily, those nice girls are always around to keep them occupied.
Oh, hey!
That's them over there!
This'll be fun!
Okay, let's do it!
It's Braun Shushu!
I like your hairpiece, number six!
Thank you!
Everybody sit down by me!
What are they gonna sing?
You twerps ain't ready for this!
I need it!
Hey, check it out!
I think this is just about everybody!
Make room, okay?
Alright, it's showtime.
We're gonna sing a couple songs for you guys, so eyes up here, okay?
One, two, three, four!
Awaken, returner!
Let your heartfelt desire!
A longing for miracles that can inspire!
Gotta get it right if we're gonna survive!
Never gonna stop with a dud and run live!
Livin' life the best we can!
Goin' down our destined path!
Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do!
Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do!
Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do!
Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do!
Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do-Do!
Huh?
Huh, hmmm!
Boop!
Have you been performing every evening?
Yeah, we have actually!
During the day we help out with getting the chores done,
and then at night we put on a little show for the kids, you know?
It must be a great show. I saw lots of smiles.
Oh, I mean, it's no big deal.
We're just trying to do whatever we can to make things a little easier here.
Number two, you're the leader.
Can you tell us how this whole thing started?
Listen, pal, when crap gets rough, you gotta do what you gotta do!
Well, you really have a way with words, huh?
You brought them back to life without their permission.
I have to stop you from trying to profit off these poor deceased girls.
Uh, you know what I mean. We're just doing what we have to do.
Who could?
Still alive.
I won't die.
Yoo-hoo! Anybody down here?
I hope not, cause my pants are already soaked through and I'd prefer to leave!
Come help us! Please, we're down here!
Alright!
Wait, where are you? Keep making noises!
We're right over here! I'm gonna say!
Hold on a second! Help is on the way, sir!
Please look after him.
Sure, but what about you?
I have somewhere important I need to be right now.
Uh, wait, don't go! I have several questions to ask you!
Not that you'll listen, but please don't be foolish!
You're gonna live, old friend.
Because Franz Shushu is about to save Saga.
Let's each do our best again today!
Yeah!
Hmph...
...
Those things you don't need..
..when I see it...
love and surprise...
Because I understand.
Either this part is over, I will do so much for a long time.
Now you are just making here
You will have no pain
To be told in many times
You have laughter
Trade on
Sada wa suteranai
Hatega naku te mo
I asked Machiko for some makeup so that might work for now
That's what I thought if it's not our special kind it won't stick
And what we did have is certain to fall off during our performance later
So the masks won't do us much good at that point
Everyone's looking forward to this show though
That's what they look like
But I don't want to give up just like that
Hell no
I agree
We must think of a safe way to proceed
Exactly
I'm with you guys
Still we can't go on looking like this
If only we had masks to hide more than just the nose and mouth
There's a toy store in this mall somewhere isn't there? They might have them
That would be a good idea
But the stores aren't open right now
Okay, so we break in obviously
We aren't those kind of zombies
Damn it! What are we supposed to do?
How about we don't go straight to full-on marceny?
What?
The Osaki doll paint
I've got it!
We can make our own masks
Yeah
What the heck are they trying to do?
Hey Saga, we're Franchushu! We're gonna give you the best performance we can so be sure to cheer super loud for us okay?
Is it not working?
Don't these crazy girls think about the risks at all?
They're like dolls
Oh that's right
Yes
They get it
I think we're good
It's going over better than I thought
We didn't bake them enough
Let's use them more
And go!
We're our Franchushu!
Crap! We screwed up big time! The eye holes made them less durable! We did a poor job!
That isn't the main issue!
They put this right under the cold deck's faces!
There's gotta be a way to play it off, right?
Now they've done it!
Well, since it already happened, we just have to come clean
Listen guys, we hid this from you, and we're really sorry!
The truth is…
Your faces look bad! Did you get hurt?
Huh?
We're actually… zombies
That can't be right, because zombies are scary!
Yeah, zombies eat people! I saw it in a movie!
Oh!
You're not scary, so you can't be zombies. You must be something else!
Right! Let's decide what they are!
Um!
oh…
You're Frans Shushu!
yep!
There are Frans Shushu!
There's nothin' else to it!
Go Frans Shushu!
Oh!
You got it!
Wait what?
Wait, what?
We tried to scare you with zombie makeup,
but you're just too smart.
Really?
That was funny.
Okay, you guys.
Are you ready to have some fun?
Yeah!
Front choo-choo!
Sweet!
We're gonna rock this mall again today,
so get excited!
Yay!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
It's not that they didn't consider the risk.
They're risking more than I can imagine
every time they step on stage,
but to them,
it's worth it to have a chance to convey
how they feel deep inside.
Dead or alive,
Front choo-choo are idols.
Take away all the bells and whistles,
look at the pure remains and the bare bones,
And what's left is what an idol truly is.
So, Okoba, if you would, I'd like for you to help us out.
I thought we were done for.
We faked our way through.
These kids really saved the day.
It truly is a blessing to have the crowd's admiration.
What about tomorrow, though?
The masks should be more durable if we bake them for longer.
That's not what she meant.
What else can we do?
Don't cry.
Forget about the creepy masks already.
Where'd you come from?
What the hell, man?
So now you show up?
Do you have any idea what we've been through without you here?
Because of your absence, we were forced to rush the delicate process of doll making.
Again, you're missing the point.
You're so late!
Rrrr, rrrr, rrrr.
Eh, you'll get over it.
Now line up single file for your makeup jobs.
You zombies are looking seriously crusty.
I haven't given up on you, by the way.
On the 8th of March, you are still doing your event show.
Even after all this?
To me, this is all the more reason we need to.
Your performance tonight made me realize that fact.
What Saga needs most right now is to see you girls singing.
The adults are waiting.
The children are waiting, too.
You are idols, after all.
You brought smiles to people in this difficult time, so I know you can do it.
That said, we're obviously working at a disadvantage.
And we won't have time to rehearse on concert day, so you'll have to come in cold.
Is that…
It's fine.
It'll be tough, but we'd do anything to help the people of Saga.
And if it came to it, we would risk our lives.
I mean, you're dead, but that's cool.
Anyway, the show's in 16 days.
Call time is 10 a.m. sharp.
I'll do everything humanly possible to help, and you do everything zombily possible.
Got it?
Mr. Kotaro!
What is it?
I just realized there's something that I never said to you.
In spite of everything, you never gave up on us.
Well, I mean, except that one time, I guess.
What I mean is, we only made it this far because we had you to keep pulling us along.
Back when I was alive, I was so moved by watching Ai,
and then I got to meet Mai Mai,
who said that she felt the same way because she saw my performances.
Anyway, I know everything's been a total mess
ever since that crazy rainstorm hit Saga,
but entertaining people at the shelter has been …
Well, for the first time, it feels like I have a real reason to sing, you know?
I mean, since turning into a zombie.
And I guess I just wanted to say …
I'm so glad that you made me an idol.
I owe you so much for that.
Oh, Inui, thank you.
Oh, Inui, thank you so much for being here.
Listen …
Hm?
I …
Could you speak up?
I've got what it takes, and don't you ever forget that!
Oh!
Look, Sakura, I lied when I said that you didn't have it.
And for as long as Franshushu exists,
I promise I'll be someone who has it too!
And Sakura, the truth is, EFS is just the start!
Cause your dream …
Franshushu's dream …
It is bigger!
One day you'll be loved by the whole world!
Until then, I give my undying word …
I …
…
Sakura here!
If Saga needs us, then we'll sing with everything we've got!
Nothing can stop us from standing up for our home!
Next time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, Episode 12,
The Greatest Saga in History!
Saga is eternal!
…